JOSEPH CRISTIAM CANEPA PORTAL

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: November 24, 1974

Passport: 116458785

Linked In: https://pe.linkedin.com/in/joseph-canepa-58143b108

https://pe.linkedin.com/in/joseph-canepa-97902221

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Expert in the activities of the tourism market and comprehensive management of operations.

Customer service-oriented in Travel and Tourism industries with experience over 10 years. Possesses expertise in strategic partnership identification and development event planning and travel coordination.

Possess strong knowledge of the software development and IT product design lifecycle.

Key skills include time management organization and written and verbal communication.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2007- Present

Director/ Shareholder

ATLAS CORP & ASOCIADOS SAC

- Seek business partner around the world
- Provide strategic planning, international business development
- Create strategic alliances with suppliers globally.

2013- Present

Director/ Shareholder

CARISMA VIAJES PERU SAC (www.viajescarisma.com)

- Identify new business opportunities, participate in new business pitches and assist in drafting new business proposals
- Involved in managing strategies for employees' professional development.
- Identify and lead new business opportunities.

2002 - 2007

Sales Manger

COSTAMAR TRAVEL

- Actively assisted business department in meeting goals
- Providing exceptional in store experience for customers
- Received clients on behalf of the director/manager and assisted them in solving common problems

2001-2002

Sales Manager

CARRUSEL REPRESENTACIONES

- Preside over operations.
- Managed and supervised firm operations on a daily basis
- Facilitated development and operations

2000-2001

Sales Manger

PAN AMERICAN ASSISTANCE

- Met with customers to discuss travel foreign and domestic travel and tour packages.
- Calculated travel and accommodation costs within customer budget and offered recommendations for cost savings such as off-season tours.
- Provided travel brochures and destination literature with points of interest relevant to customer needs.

FORMAL EDUCATION

1997

UIGV LIMA - Bachelors in Business Administration

EXPERTISE

Office Tools

Management systems

Applicative AFIP, BCRA